Opening.
Now it's started, Upcomi. This time we're joined by Ayano Kawamura from Angerme and Yumi Kasai from Tsubaki Factory.
This programme goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will bring you the process of production, including our recordings and rehearsals.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Kawamura, am working hard at rehearsals for the autumn tour.
New members Miika Shimoita and Hana Goto have joined us,
This is the first time for me to take part in a concert with full participation,
I'm working very hard with the older members in rehearsals, communicating with them very well,
The title of this autumn tour is '11 Angels',
I think this autumn tour will be a concert where we can present the 11 members of Angerme and I think it will be a concert that everyone can enjoy,
We are working very hard in rehearsals.
I've talked to two of Angerme's new members, Hana Goto and Miika Shimoita,
I've spoken to Hana Goto and Miika Shimoita, two of the newest members of Angerme, and they are so energetic and cute, and I think they work really hard at rehearsals.
They are always cheerful and cheerful, and I always get smiles from them, which makes me work hard at rehearsals.
I, Kana, have recently become addicted to stretching to improve my posture, and I've been doing it for three weeks,
I've been watching videos and going to the osteopath to correct my posture.
I've been going to the osteopath,
I do a lot of things, I watch stretching videos and do it every night.
Wow, that's great.
I've heard that stretching is very important now,
It's amazing that you've been doing it for three weeks.
That's right. I'm surprisingly the kind of person who doesn't continue, but I've been doing it for three weeks,
I think my posture has improved a bit.
Also, when I want to improve my posture, I try wearing a corset,
When I want to correct my posture, I try wearing a corset or wearing this kind of back-bearing device,
I try my best to correct my posture.
I'll try to refer to them.
Let's start with this issue of APUKAMI.
Tsubaki Factory It's My Life It's My Life Music Video Filming Making
It will be released on 27 September.
Watch the making of the music video shoot for Yuuki It's My Life, from Tsubaki Factory's latest single.
Good morning. Please give my regards to you.
Nice to meet you.
Basically, we didn't move our feet, but there was a little bit of hand gesture, because the song is pretty much a song,
It's quite a song, so it's okay to go hard against the camera at times,
Or you can shake it out?
You can shake it out. Hand gestures are totally fine.
What if you can't?
If you can't, you're not facing the camera at all,
Not at all, just like us, off-camera,
Can I sing like that?
Yes, you can.
Thank you for watching.
Proof that you've come a long way.
The filming of the music video for Yuki Ittsumai Life has begun.
First we shot a scene like that, and then we shot a scene like that.
We shot a lip scene, an image scene...
But there's water nearby.
And we were blessed with the weather.
It was a bit hot.
But it's probably the staff who are hotter than us.
We worked really hard today.
We'll do our best to make sure that the shooting goes smoothly.
Let's have fun!
Everybody in the navel, try to point towards the camera.
Here we go, ladies, action!
Let's jump when I raise it once.
Jump when I raise it.
Here we go! Ready!
Yeah!
I can run!
We went round the lip scene of Yuki it's my life.
And the image scene.
I used some kind of cloth.
It was really fresh and fun!
I hadn't done cloth by myself for a long time.
I haven't done it in a long time.
I don't know if I did it well.
I don't know if I did it well, but I did it.
Peace and Burn?
I think I used cloth in a music video.
I used cloth in some music video, so it's been a while since I've used cloth.
Oh!
This is a rooftop.
And the view is really good.
And I heard that you can look back when you're filming, so I did.
So I turned around and there was an amazing view.
I thought I'd just keep looking backwards while we were filming.
Please look forward.
Okay, let's go.
Everyone, please wait for me.
Yes, please come back.
It's wider, it's fine.
You can all go wider.
Come on, wider.
Come on, get your parts ready.
Okay. All right.
No time, no future, whatever the future ends up being.
That's how you do it, what you think about, go and make it happen.
It's okay, no hesitation.
No more, no more, no more.
I'm not a captain.
See, but until one day, for the sake of hesitation
You'll be in my life
Garbage love H. The filament that I rejoiced in
Oh, my God!
We've just finished the dance scene, and this song is very bright and fun,
We were blessed with good weather today and the staff were very cheerful and excited, so I think we all had a lot of fun filming together,
Also, I think there are many parts where I can dance with everyone, such as the choreography of the chorus, so I hope we can do it live soon.
I really enjoyed the dance scene.
I'm still scared that I'm not full enough to Be Alright.
Gently, gently, gently have the guts to get hurt.
Don't worry, I won't give up, I don't feel like losing
Still till one day, for the tears
Hugs to Be Alright
What should I do?
Start, start, start, start!
Faster!
Yes, cut!
Start the car!
What the hell? I can be anything I want to be tomorrow.
I can be anything I want to be
Oh, anything is possible.
Oh, before you think you're ready
La La La La La La La La La La La La La La
Jump out of the way, good smile, next week...
Anything's fine, anything's fine
Each one of you has love to go out and make it happen
Don't worry, there's no hesitation
Come on!
Wow!
Oh!
Let's do it!
Just try!
Still wait sometime for the lost
No giving up
You're working it's my life
And my life
Well then, with this cut, we've come to the end of the shoot.
Thank you very much.
Yes, we've just finished shooting the music video for Yuki it's my life.
Unfortunately Yume Kishimoto wasn't here today,
We were all able to work hard together in the dream culture.
This song is about me and Yume-chan Kishimoto's graduation,
The song is based on the image of me and Yume-chan Kishimoto's graduation,
But, it's also very emotional,
But by singing them cheerfully, I think it brings out the emo side of the song,
I want everyone to pay attention to it,
Also, you were filming outside today.
It was a beautiful sunny day. It was a crazy sunny day.
It was a beautiful day for the shoot, and I thought that Tsubaki is a sunny girl.
It was a very fulfilling and enjoyable graduation today.
Thank you very much.
YUIKI! It's My Life!" is the graduation song of the member Riko Yamagishi,
It's a refreshing, summery song,
It's a refreshing, summery song with positive, forward-looking lyrics that will push you forward,
I hope you will pay attention to the lyrics,
The music video was quite hot,
We danced on the rooftop,
It was quite hot and we danced on the rooftop and everyone got sunburnt,
I think it will create great summer memories.
Now that I've seen the making of the video, I can feel from the footage that it was an amazing period of time,
You can feel how hot it was,
The rest of the filming was done with this cloth.
Everyone seemed to be having a lot of fun filming,
But the finished music video also looked really fun,
The finished music video also showed everyone having a great time and smiling,
It was really refreshing,
I thought it was a song that really pushed me forward,
I want to watch this music video a lot when I want to cheer myself up.
This is Tsubaki Factory Yuuki it's my life The making of the music video shoot.
Let's play Lovely music Let's dance Disco till morning Let's
Juice! Funky Flossing Now on sale
Having fun? Watch the rest of the show!
Here's what's next. Vocal recording for Tea Horse's latest single
From the latest single by Ochanoma, Ochanoma, Magical place, Let's go, Showa and 2025 are all here.
石栗香奈美のボーカルレコーディングの様子をご覧ください
Okay, I'll do it then. First of all, the A melody. I'm going to do it up to the 2021 tune.
Isonoke, sakurake, the jab platform that surrounds the three generations
(How many generations watched the same programme on TV?
The matrials and choices have widened, and what we want to watch has become more varied.
But it's much easier than it used to be to be closely connected Reiwatane
# I want to be relieved
Yes, it's almost enough, but...
That isonoketata sakuraketatasan in your head...
I want to emphasise the part of your head that's stuck in your head.
Yes, sir.
And the matri...
And the choices.
And the hiccups and the hee...
Yes.
And Shawatane and Reiwatane accentuate it a lot.
And, well, it's almost done.
The TV in
But
Far from it.
Why is it
by far.
Think of the teeth as low
Far.
Far?
Yes, ma'am.
Insonoke, Sakurake, three generations of jabberdabbers.
How they all watched the same show on the same TV set.
Mad Lingo, washing paper, all spread out, all wanting to watch different things.
But it's much more immediate and close-knit than it used to be.
I'm so relieved.
Here you go... and here you go.
Yes, sir.
Okay, B melody.
It's not supposed to be there.
I'll do the B-melody later.
Yes.
Why?
So far...
It's only Riping!
Just the ripping!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Only liping!
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes, yes.
But it's much easier to get to know each other in peace than in the past.
I'm relieved.
Human cats are still the same.
Where can I be myself?
Riping's all you've got.
Only the last pitch is a palm.
Only Riping!
That's it.
It's just ripping!
Yes.
Yes, then only!
Only liping!
Sorry.
And don't make him any weaker, just listen to him as he is.
Yes.
But you're much more connected now than in the past.
I want to be relieved. I want to be relaxed.
Human cats are no different.
Where can you be yourself?
Only at the Riping!
Only at the Ri pitch.
Yes, sorry.
I'll just do the last one.
Yes, sir.
Human cats don't change.
Just the "R" pitch!
OK.
You're early.
Let's go.
It's the first rusty one, but I'll take separate shots.
Yes.
From Wacha to Mahoroba is fine.
I'll finish this Wachcha series first, and then shoot the remaining ones later.
Okay, I understand.
Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Wachcha Onnain Chanoma Sachcha Sachcha Sachcha Sachcha Mahoroba
Just sounding cool and normal, maybe even strong.
Yes.
So that the attack of Waccha's Wa or Saccha's Difference doesn't become slow and wet.
Wa no Awa no Awa doesn't follow behind
Waccha baccha baccha baccha yes
Not just in the living room
Wacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Bacchan Tea room
Sacchan sacchan sacchan sacchan sacchan sacchan sacchan sacchan Mahoroba
Yes, perfect!
Then let's have a cup of tea with Wacchan...
Yes!
Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye, Bye-bye.
Sacchan Sacchan Sacchan Sacchan Sacchan Kelu Coinmon
Batsu-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi-bachi
Online offline family, friends and boys
Online or offline O-more attacks
Online
Can you shorten it a bit more?
Online and offline
Online, online and offline.
Sharp online
Sharp and short.
Yes, okay.
Family ka too
Yes, sir.
Online Offline Meet with family, friends and passion
Mahoroba
Just one more time.
Yes.
Only o Hopefully more will come out.
Online
Why?
Online Offline
I'd like to see a lot more Attacks that sound a bit like that.
Yes, please.
Online On-line On-line
Family, friends and Jonestan
Bacchan bacchan bacchan
The end where it went up more.
It was a bit weird.
Well, I liked it better earlier.
From the comfort of your own home.
Let's do it up to the tea room.
Yes, sir.
Bak-chan-bak-chan-bak-chan, tea room.
Batcha-batcha-batcha-batcha.
It's comfortable. It's great.
Love can only be born in a place like that.
Wacha-on-cha-no ma
Yes, it was a very up-tempo song, but she didn't bite at all and sang in a way that was very clear and easy to understand, and she was very easy to listen to.
になったのが、赤青は鉛筆。ちゃんと赤の方も使ったり青の方も使ったりして、
When I was given the right instructions, I would circle the words, or cut the words in a shashashasha shasha shasha way.
I thought that the way she was drawing in response to those instructions was very Kanami Ishii-like, and it made me want to see her as a god.
It's true that Kanami Ishii's singing voice is really beautiful, and it's very comfortable to listen to.
And even though Uptemp's songs are really difficult, the rhythms are so precise that it makes me feel comfortable listening to them.
I'm really looking forward to hearing more and more of your songs.
Showa and Reimu were both wacky, it was a vocal recording by Kanami Ishii!
By all means, everyone!
Thanks to you, I can do my best too!
Up papers by Ayano Kawamura of Angerme and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
And now, here we go.
Angerme Doukou student vocal recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording session of Angerme doukou student Wakana Matsumoto from the latest Angerme single.
Yes, please.
Like that girl, I'm sure everyone seems better than me.
I see that feeling when I play.
Hmm?
Yes. - Yes?
Yes, ma'am.
Like her, I'm sure everyone looks better than me.
I don't show it when I play.
The length of the final cut was very important and so on,
I was also asked to use my breath to cut the last boyne sound,
Personally, I'm not very good at the 'a' and 'o' in the voicings,
I'm personally not very good at the "a" and "o" of the voicings, so it was very difficult to cut them.
I got scared.
Yes, but...
But... but...
Yes!
You're genuinely kind.
Though I was frightened of betrayal if I trusted you.
I was frightened of betrayal if I trusted you.
You're genuinely kind.
You said you could do three a day, three a day.
It's a bit different from what I'm used to.
I wasn't really aware of it.
It was strange and difficult.
It was a little bit towards the chorus
It was getting brighter and brighter towards the chorus, so I had to pay attention to the feeling of raising the tension a bit.
I paid attention to the feeling of raising the tension a little bit at a time.
Around the first verse
Yes, I did.
I can't love you
I'm sorry I doubted you.
I love you
I don't know how happy
I've been so happy.
I know how happy you are
How happy were you?
How much, actually.
How much, actually?
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
I love you I know how happy you were
About...
Yes, I do.
I love you, actually.
I had to sing the song with the most tension and cheerfulness, and I had to sing the back notes very carefully, so I think that part was very difficult,
It's a really lovely warm song, so I want to keep working hard so that it becomes a good song and I can sing it well.
Aa-te-eru-u Yes.
I know you were happy.
This is the first time I've sung a Tsunku III song,
This is how I'm going to sing through Tsunku III's songs on Takeuchi-san's last single,
I'm really looking forward to singing wonderful songs with Takeuchi-san on his last single,
I want to sing it with care.
Thank you very much.
Yes, this song was written by Atsunku, so it's a song that I sing with a greater awareness of rhythm than the usual Angerme songs,
From the time of recording, Kazunade-chan was cutting the rhythm perfectly,
I also thought that she was very good at ending words and removing the last part of phrases, and that's just the way she is.
Matsumoto-san's sense of rhythm is very good, and when I was listening to it, I thought the places where she cut were also very good,
But even more than that, the pitch of the notes is too good, and I think some people get a little blurred when it comes to the higher parts,
I thought it was really cool that Matsumoto was able to hit it with such pinpoint accuracy.
This was the vocal recording of Angerme alumna Wakana Matsumoto.
Tea lady! New single
Tea Aunt! Mahalo baika enoba!
Showa mo 2025 mo Wachamacha!
Now on sale!
Don't overdo it and take care of yourself!
It's time to say goodbye to UPKAMI, brought to you by Aino Kawamura and Yumi Kasai!
We've seen a lot of footage this time too.
I, Kasai, was left with a great impression of the making of the music video for the Organic It's My Life shoot.
It was the last music video with Mr. Yamagishi, so...
It was also very memorable.
It was very memorable that we shot it on the rooftop, so I think it was a great experience.
I think it was a great experience.
It's my life! It's my life! We'll be releasing three AAA singles on 27 September.
We'll be releasing them as an AAA single, so please check them out!
I, Kawamura, saw Kanon Ishiguri and Shigeru Matsumoto's recording,
They both hear the words very clearly and are easy to understand,
I discovered that they both sing in a way that makes it easy to hear and understand the words,
After watching the recording, I watched the music video again,
I wanted to immerse myself in this song.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Apple Ronto Group.
We'll be introducing you to parts of their work that you wouldn't normally see, so please subscribe to our channel.
This time on upcami, my partners were Aino Kawamura of Angerme and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
Farewell.
It's the season, a woman's heart and
Summer sky Kimokimo Kimokimo